premiumcoding.com 2018-09-07

# PRIVACY POLICY - PremiumCoding

Last Updated 22.5.2018

The Premiumcoding Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services. Premiumcoding references in this document to “us,” “our,” and “we”.

#### WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

When you visit our website you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and website use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse the site.

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION YOU CHOOSE TO PROVIDE

**Registration Information**

You will provide us information about yourself, your firm or company, and your practices when you purchase Premiumcoding products and services or register for email newsletters and alerts.

When you register to our site we are collecting your mail, name, last name, a nickname by default. Other personal data can be added via your profile on our site. All personal data are stored in our database.

If you are registering for the support and you have bought theme via Envato or Mojo marketplace we are collecting your name, last name, email, and your purchase code. All this data are saved in our database.

If you are under 16 years of age you  **MUST**  obtain parental consent before you can register to our site.

**Purchase Information**

All purchases are made via FastSpring.com. We consider FastSpring to be a third party data processor. After you make the purchase we are storing only your email, first name, last name and purchase information like what you have bought from us, how much you have paid, when did you buy it.

You can read about FastSpring Privacy Policy on this[ link](https://fastspring.com/privacy/).

If you are under 16 years of age you  **MUST**  obtain parental consent before you can make purchases via our site.

**Support Information**

We are sending your name, email, technical data, theme name, subject, message and my purchase codes to Zendesk.com via a secure and encrypted connection. We use Zendesk.com for our support system. We are not storing your Subject and Message to PremiumCoding database. How your personal information are handled via Zendesk you can read on this [link.](https://www.zendesk.com/company/customers-partners/eu-data-protection/) This also applies to replying to this ticket. If you wish to delete all of your tickets you can anytime send us [requesting removal support data](https://premiumcoding.com/contact-2/)“. Please add to subject DELETE ALL MY TICKETS GDPR” and we will remove all information about your support tickets.

If you are under 16 years of age you  **MUST**  obtain parental consent before you can use our support system.

**Email  newsletter**

If you choose to join our email newsletter, the email address that you submit to us will be forwarded to [MailChimp](https://mailchimp.com/) who provide us with email marketing services. We consider MailChimp to be a third party data processor. The email address that you submit will not be stored within this website’s own database or in any of our internal computer systems.

Your email address will remain within MailChimp’s database for as long as we continue to use MailChimp’s services for email marketing or until you specifically request removal from the list. You can do this by unsubscribing using the unsubscribe links contained in any email newsletters that we send you or by [requesting removal via email](https://premiumcoding.com/contact-2/). When requesting removal via email, please send your email to us using the email account that is subscribed to the mailing list.

If you are under 16 years of age you  **MUST**  obtain parental consent before joining our email newsletter.

While your email address remains within the MailChimp database, you will receive periodic (approximately one per week) newsletter-style emails from us.

**Affiliate Privacy Policy**

We take your privacy seriously and take measures to provide all users of the PremiumCoding Affiliate platform with a safe and secure environment. This starts with requiring only basic information to join our service, and the ability to use pseudonyms and usernames

When this policy mentions “we” or “us,” it refers to the controller of your information under this policy. Your information is controlled by PremiumCoding Affiliate.

You should read this entire policy to learn more about how we handle privacy, data, and how we use any information that you provide. However, here are a few key points.

  * We require only basic information from you including name, email, and username to create an account with our service. You may use any information you wish, including pseudonyms if you would like to remain anonymous. We are also collecting payment email, your website URL, and information how you will promote us, but those fields are optional so you can leave it empty. All these information are stored in PremiumCoding database.
  * Any personal information entered into the system can be updated and reviewed at any time from your account [settings page](https://premiumcoding.com/wp-admin/profile.php). You may change this information at any time, or disable your account entirely and remove any personally identifiable information within our internal systems.

If you are under 16 years of age you  **MUST**  obtain parental consent before joining our Affiliate platform.

**SERVER LOCATTION (database location)**

PremiumCoding server is located in Strasbourg, France in the Datadock Datacenter. Which is owned and operated by Host Europe GmbH located in Germany.

#### WEBSITE USE INFORMATION

Similar to other commercial websites, this site utilizes a standard technology called “cookies” (see explanation below, “What Are Cookies?”) and Web server logs to collect information about how this site is used. Information gathered through cookies and web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at this site, and the websites visited just before and just after our site. We, our advertisers and ad serving companies may also use small technology or pieces of code to determine which advertisements and promotions users have seen and how users responded to them.

We also collect theme usage data through our automatic update mechanism, which checks to insure you have the latest version of the theme you’ve purchased. This process is necessary in order to provide you with a painless and consistent upgrade experience. You can opt out of receiving automatic updates to the latest version of your theme by disabling updates in your Theme Settings.

#### WHAT ARE COOKIES?

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a website, that site’s computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a website to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies that originate from their sites. We have no access or control over those cookies.

#### HOW DO WE USE INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM COOKIES?

As you use this website, the site uses its cookies to differentiate you from other users. In some cases, we also use cookies to prevent you from seeing unnecessary advertisements or requiring you to log in more than is necessary for security. Cookies, in conjunction with our web server’s log files, allow us to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting this site and which parts of the site are most popular. This helps us gather feedback in order to constantly improve this site and better serve our customers.

We have prepared a list of all cookies that are used on PremiumCoding.com site and option where you can withdraw your consent. Check [cookie list](https://premiumcoding.com/cookies-used-on-premiumcoding-com/).

#### SHARING INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES

The information we collect is used to improve the content of this site and the quality of our service and is not shared with or sold to other organizations for commercial purposes. That being said, your information could be shared under the following circumstances:

  * We use third parties to facilitate our business, including, but not limited to, sending email and processing payments. In connection with these offerings and business operations, these third parties may have access to your personal information for use in connection with those business activities.
  * If it becomes necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law.

#### HOW DO WE SECURE INFORMATION TRANSMISSIONS?

Email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication. For this reason, we request that you do not send private information to us by email. Some of the information you may enter on this site may be transmitted securely via Secure Sockets Layer SSL, 128 bit encryption services. Pages utilizing this technology will have URLs that start with HTTPS instead of HTTP.

#### WHAT ABOUT OTHER WEBSITES LINKED TO THIS SITE?

We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our site nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other websites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our site. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our site to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including sites which have a link on our site, is subject to that website’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

#### YOUR CONSENT

By using this site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on this site to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it.

**DELITING YOUR PERSONAL DATA**

If you wish you can anytime send us [requesting removal personal data](https://premiumcoding.com/contact-2/). Please add to subject “REMOVAL OF ALL PERSONAL INFORMATIONS” and we will delete all of your data in our database.
